Finding Aid of the WUWM Records, 1950-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- WUWM Records, 1950-2014, UWM Archival Collection 2; 9.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes, including 227 audio reels and 161 audio cassettes) 398 digital audio files (96.2 GB)
  - 4. WUWM Grass Roots, 1964-1967
    - McCarthy, Eugene, Keynote Address at UWM, January 19, 1967, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Metropolitan Sewerage Commission, November 9, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Milwaukee Bar Association, with Reuster, James and Hankin, Spring 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 130-131)
    - Milwaukee Clerk of Courts, with McCormick and Jury Commissioner Dostal, May 17, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 132-133)
    - Milwaukee Commission on Community Relations, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Milwaukee County and Circuit Courts, Judge Landry, March 14, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Milwaukee County Board of Supervisors, with Grecco and Grobschmidt, April 25, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 136-137)
    - Milwaukee County Civil Defense, with Jeske, Grobschmidt, Grecco, May 4, 1964, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Milwaukee County Civil Service, with Anthony P. Ramand, undated, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 139-140)
    - Milwaukee County Clerk, with Clement F. Mihalski, October 12, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Milwaukee County Clerk Race, with Lloyd LeRay, Jr., October 25, 1966, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 142-143)
    - Milwaukee County Corporation Council, with John Devitt and Mike Barron, September 20, 1965, Audio reel (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Milwaukee County Election Committee, with Eunice Neimi, January 3, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 145-146)
    - Milwaukee County Executive, with John Doyne, Webber, Gill, April 20, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - Milwaukee County Executive, with John Doyne and Financial Committee Chairman Pohl, County Budget, October 19, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 148-149)
    - Milwaukee County Executive John Doyne, State of the County Address, May 31, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 150-151)
    - Milwaukee County Family Court, with Leander Foley and Robert Hanson, May 2, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 152-153)
    - Milwaukee County Institutions and Departments, with Guenther, Mundy and O'Donnel, August 24, 1965 and August 26, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Milwaukee County Legislative Committee, with Gerard Paradowski and Richard Nowakowski, undated, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 155-156)
    - Milwaukee County Medical Services, Institutions and You, with Dr. Harold E. Cook and James Doyne, May 25, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Milwaukee County Mental Health Services, with Dr. H. Landes and Mary Holand, June 1, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Milwaukee County Parks, Extra Material, May 7, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Milwaukee County Parks, Recreation and You, May 7, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Milwaukee County Probate Court, with Mudrock and Sullivan, March 8, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 161-162)
    - Milwaukee County Register of Deeds, October 26, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Milwaukee County Sherriff Candidates, September 8, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Milwaukee County Sherriff, with Michael Wolke, June 14, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 165-166)
    - Milwaukee County Superintendent of Schools, with Michael Keyes and Helen Olsen, June 22, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Milwaukee County Treasurer Barczak and County Auditor Boos, October 5, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - Milwaukee Federal Courts, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 169-170)
    - Milwaukee School Board, March 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Milwaukee Traffic Court Race, with Krueger vs. Ziperski, February 21, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 172-173)
    - Misdemeanor Court, with Christ Seraphim, April 25, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Moser, Tilton, etc., January 27, 1966, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Nelson, Gaylord, June 19, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Nelson, Gaylord at Labor Dinner, June 19, 1965, Audio reel (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Nelson, Gaylord, January 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 181-182)
    - Office of Management and Budget Analysis, September 28, 1965, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - Okarskin Speech, Republican Convention, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - Political Parties in Wisconsin, Local Party Chairs, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 185-186)
    - Press Conference #2, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Prison Wrap Up, with Warden Burke, June 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 188-189)
    - Probation - Federal, State and County, with Kegel, May 14, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 190-191)
    - Register of Deeds Race, September 8, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Republican Convention, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Republican Convention, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 194-195)
    - Republican Mock Vote, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Reuss, Henry, January 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Scott, Leule, Speech and Question and Answer, Minority Housing, Spring 1965, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Sorensen, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 199-200)
    - State Supreme Court Race, with Halloway, Harry, Spring 1967, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - State Treasurer Race, with Richard J. Zaborski, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - Taycheedah, Wisconsin's Home for Women, with Superintendent McCauley, June 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 203-204)
    - Taylor, Maxwell, October 14, 1965, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 205-206)
    - Wallenberg, Rothwell Interview, March 1965, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Waupun State Prison, undated, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - Waupun State Prison, June 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 209-212)
    - Wisconsin Senate District 3, with Wayne Styza, October 27, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 213-214)
    - Wisconsin Senate District 5 Race, with Wilfred Schuele, November 1, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 215-216)
    - Wisconsin Senate District 7, with Leland S. McParland and Dean Mall, September 27, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Wisconsin Senate District 9 Race, with Daehn, Sussman, Little, 1966, Audio reel (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - Wisconsin Senate District 11 Race, with Wayne Whitton, 1966, Audio reel (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Your Role in a Political Party in Wisconsin, April 8, 1965, Audio reel (Box 11, Folder 220)
    - Zablocki, Clement, Democratic Fund Raising, undated, Audio reel (Box 11, Folder 221)
    - Zablocki, Clement, December 27, 1965, Audio reel (Box 11, Folder 222-223)
  - 5. WUWM Miscellaneous Programs, 1974-1975
    - Concert of Storage and Retrieval, January 10, 1975, Audio reel (Box 12, Folder 224)
    - Fromkin, "Third Party," undated, Audio reel (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - Health Spas Interview, with Breast Cancer Self Exam, November 1974, Audio reel (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - Park Presentations, undated, Audio reel (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - 6. WUWM East Side Issues, 1977-1982
    - Side 1, Jan. 13, 1977; Side 2, Jan. 20, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 228)
    - Side 1, Jan. 27, 1977; Side 2, Feb. 3, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 229)
    - Side 1, Feb. 10, 1977; Side 2, Feb. 24, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 230)
    - Side 1, Mar. 3, 1977; Side 2, Mar. 10, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 231)
    - Side 1, Mar. 17, 1977; Side 2, Mar. 24, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 232)
    - Side 1, Mar. 3, 1977; Side 2, Apr. 7, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 233)
    - Side 1, Apr. 14, 1977; Side 2, Apr. 21, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 234)
    - Side 1, Apr. 28, 1977; Side 2, May 19, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 235)
    - Side 1, May 26, 1977; Side 2, June 2, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 236)
    - Side 1, June 9, 1977; Side 2, June 16, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 237)
    - Side 1, June 23, 1977; Side 2, June 30, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 238)
    - Side 1, July 7, 1977; Side 2, July 14, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 239)
    - Side 1, July 21, 1977; Side 2, July 28, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 240)
    - Side 1, Aug. 4, 1977; Side 2, Oct. 6, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 241)
    - Side 1 and 2, Aug. 11, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 242)
    - Side 1 and 2, Aug. 18, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 243)
    - Side 1 and 2, Aug. 25, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 244)
    - Side 1, Sept. 1, 1977; Side 2: Shorewood Assessment, Feb. 2, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 245)
    - Side 1: West of the River House and Home Improvement, Sept. 15, 1977; Side 2: Century Hall, Sept. 22, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 246)
    - Side 1, Sept. 29, 1977; Side 2, Oct. 4, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 247)
    - Side 1, Oct. 20, 1977; Side 2, Oct. 13, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 248)
    - Side 1, Oct. 27, 1977; Side 2, Nov. 2, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Folder 249)
    - Side 1: Housing Conditions, Nov. 15, 1977; Side 2: Credit Union, Nov. 17, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 250)
    - Side 1: First HUB Credit Union, Nov. 24, 1977; Side 2, Dec. 29, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 251)
    - Side 1 and 2: Desegregation, Dec. 1, 1977, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 252)
    - Side 1: Metropolitan Milwaukee Fair Housing Council, Dec. 29, 1977; Side 2: Bus Shelter Program, Jan. 5, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 253)
    - Side 1: Parking and Transit, Jan. 12, 1978; Side 2: Alcohol Abuse Among Youth, I., Jan. 19, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 254)
    - Side 1: Traffic Flow Around UWM; Side 2: UWM Day Care, Feb. 23, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 255)
    - Side 1: Programs for Dealing with Alcoholism, Jan. 26, 1978; Reasons for Reassessment, Feb. 9, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 256)
    - Side 1: Reassessment, Feb. 2, 1978; Downer Ave. Parking Committee Report, Mar. 16, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 257)
    - Side 1: Reassessment, Feb. 9, 1978; UWM Day Care, Feb. 23, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 258)
    - Side 1: Community Day Care, Mar. 2, 1978; Side 2: Status Report of East Side Transit Study, Apr. 27, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 259)
    - Side 1: New Bus Shelter Program, Mar. 23, 1978; Side 2: Property Tax, Mar. 30, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 260)
    - Side 1: Reassessment, Apr. 6, 1978; Side 2: Neighborhood Pride, Apr. 20, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 261)
    - Side 1: East Side Citizens Association Assessment(?) Fair, May 18, 1978; Side 2: Milwaukee Humanities Program, June 8, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 262)
    - Side 1: Shorewood Mall, June 22, 1978; Side 2: Milwaukee Presentation Policy, June 15, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 263)
    - Side 1: Shorewood Day Plans, June 29, 1978; Side 2: Columbia Hospital, July 6, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 264)
    - Side 1: Programs for the Elderly I, July 13, 1978; Side 2: Programs for the Elderly II, July 20, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 265)
    - Side 1: Moody-Miller Debate, Nov. 2, 1978; Side 2: Home Improvement, Nov. 16, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 266)
    - Side 1: Drug Paraphernalia, Nov. 3, 1978; West River Plan, Dec. 5, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 267)
    - Side 1: Exam Stress, Dec. 13, 1978; Side 2, Dec. 13, 1978; Humanities Grant Program, Jan. 11, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 268)
    - Side 1 and 2: Exam Stress, Dec. 14, 1978- Dec. 17, 1978, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 269)
    - Side 1 and 2: Humanities, Jan. 11, 1979-Jan. 14, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 270)
    - Side 1, Mar. 15, 1979; Side 2: Sewer Suit, Mar. 8, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 271)
    - Side 1: ESCC Home Improvement Program, undated; Side 2: Transit Study Update, Aug. 29, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 272)
    - Side 1: Lake front Development, Sept. 20, 1979; Side 2: Redevelopment, Sept. 27, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 273)
    - Side 1: Health Care, Oct. 1979; Rape and Violent Crime, undated, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 274)
    - Side 1: Sewer System, Oct. 19, 1979; Side 2: Recreation, Oct. 20, 1979, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 275)
    - Sides 1 and 2: Ethnic Forum, UWM, Feb. 27, 1982, 1 audio cassette (Box 14, Folder 276-277)
  - 7. WUWM University Roundtable, 1991-2001
    - Undergraduate Education, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, undated, 1 audio cassette (Audio 278)
    - Political Correctness, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, October 3, 1991, 1 audio cassette (Audio 279)
    - Proposal To Move Classes At Civic Center To Grand Avenue Mall, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, January 2, 1992, 1 audio cassette (Audio 280)
    - Construction On Campus, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, September 3, 1992, 1 audio cassette (Audio 281)
    - Dr. Pillsbury Tenure Controversy, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, December 3, 1992, 1 audio cassette (Audio 282)
    - Sexual Discrimination Awareness, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, February 4, 1993, 1 audio cassette (Audio 283)
    - Improvements to UWM Campus/Federal Contract Compliance, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, September/October 10, 1993, 1 audio cassette (Audio 284)
    - UWM's Ranking in the US, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, November 1993, 1 audio cassette (Audio 285)
    - Accountability, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, December 1993, 1 audio cassette (Audio 286)
    - Light Rail Discussion In Milwaukee, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, February 1994, 1 audio cassette (Audio 287)
    - Public Speakers On Campus And Security, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, April 1994, 1 audio cassette (Audio 288)
    - UWM and the Carnegie Foundation Ratings, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, May 1994, 1 audio cassette (Audio 289)
    - UWM Financial Situation/Tuition Increases, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, October/November, 1994, 1 audio cassette (Audio 290)
    - The Future of UWM's Budget/Joe Klotsche, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, December 1994/March 1995, 1 audio cassette (Audio 291)
    - UW System Budget Cuts, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, April/May 1995, 1 audio cassette (Audio 292)
    - The New School Year, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, September 1995, 1 audio cassette (Audio 293)
    - UWM Open House, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, October 1995, 1 audio cassette (Audio 294)
    - UWM Times Racist Article Controversy, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, November 1995, 1 audio cassette (Audio 295)
    - Withholding Fees, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, January 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 296)
    - Strategic Planning, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, February 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 297)
    - Groups Recommending Changes to UW System, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, March 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 298)
    - Board Of Regents, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, April 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 299)
    - UWM's Enrollment Numbers, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, May 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 300)
    - Decreasing Enrollment Rates Among Upperclassmen/Grad Students, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, October 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 301)
    - Increasing Tuition Rates, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, November 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 302)
    - UWM's Budget Status, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, December 1996, 1 audio cassette (Audio 303)
    - UWM and the State Biennial Budget, with Dave Edwards and John Schroeder, January 1997, 1 audio cassette (Audio 304)
    - Information Meetings For Alumni, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, February 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 305)
    - Discussion of Zimpher's Spring Address, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, March 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 306)
    - The Wisconsin Idea To The Milwaukee Idea - Wisconsin State Economy And Education Status, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, May 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 307)
    - UWM During the Summer Versus the School Year, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, June 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 308)
    - June Board of Regents Meeting, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, August 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 309)
    - Summer Programs On Campus, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, September 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 310)
    - Chancellor's Faculty Address, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, October 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 311)
    - Wisconsin Economic Summit, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, November 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 312)
    - United Way Campaign, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, December 2000, 1 audio cassette (Audio 313)
    - Graduation and Commencement, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, January 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 314)
    - UWM Basketball, with Dave Edwards and Nancy Zimpher, February 2001, 1 audio cassette (Audio 315)
  - 8. WUWM Milwaukee Ideas, 2002-2004
    - Alumni Association Events, with Tom Luljak and Barbara Flint/Val Klump, May 16, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 316)
    - The Milwaukee Idea, with Tom Luljak and Steve Percy, May 23, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 317)
    - The Future of WUWM, with Tom Luljak and Dave Edwards, May 30, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 318)
    - The College Connection, with Tom Luljak and Joe Aigner, June 13, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 319)
    - Campus Climate, with Tom Luljak and Sona Andrews, June 20, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 320)
    - Pre-College Programs, with Tom Luljak and Carl Meredith/Pam Clark, June 27, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 321)
    - The State Of Soccer, with Tom Luljak and Louie Bennett, July 11, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 322)
    - Library's Outreach/Golda Meir Library, with Tom Luljak and Peter Watson-Boone, July 18, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 323)
    - UWM Women's Basketball and Training Camps, with Tom Luljak and Sandy Botham, July 25, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 324)
    - Incoming Freshmen, with Tom Luljak and Jan Ford, August 22, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 325)
    - Parental Notification For Prescribed Contraceptives, with Tom Luljak and Diane Reddy, August 29, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 326)
    - UWM Homecoming/4th Street Forum, with Tom Luljak and Barbara Flint/Amy Watson, September 19, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 327)
    - Freshwater Forum, with Tom Luljak and Val Klump, September 26, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 328)
    - Dean Meadows/College of Letters And Science, with Tom Luljak and Richard Meadows, October 10, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 329)
    - Student Journalism Careers, with Tom Luljak and Mark Zoromski, October 24, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 330)
    - Norris Health Center, with Tom Luljak and Don Craig, October 31, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 331)
    - UWM Basketball, with Tom Luljak and Bruce Pearl/Sandy Botham, November 21, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 332)
    - Political Campaigns/Shift of Power in Washington DC, with Tom Luljak and Tom Holbrook, November 28, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 333)
    - PhD program in History, with Tom Luljak and Jeffrey Merrick, December 12, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 334)
    - TMI Initiatives in 2002/UWM's Current State, with Tom Luljak and Steve Percy, December 19, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 335)
    - UWM Foundation/Giving To The University, with Tom Luljak and Lucia Petrie, December 26, 2002, 1 audio cassette (Audio 336)
    - Human and Animal Relationships, with Tom Luljak and Nigel Rothfels, January 9, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 337)
    - Opera and UWM's Connection to Music, with Tom Luljak and William Lavanis, January 16, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 338)
    - Union Theatre/The Appeal of Film, with Tom Luljak and Luke Sieczek, January 30, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 339)
    - Milwaukee Idea House, with Tom Luljak, February 13, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 340)
    - Black and Gold Committee, with Tom Luljak and Ruth Williams/Kory Kozloski, February 20, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 341)
    - Gerontology, with Tom Luljak and Rhonda Montgomery, February 27, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 342)
    - Terrorism and Urban Life, with Tom Luljak and Paul Rivas, March 13, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 343)
    - Cultures and Communities Certificate Program, with Tom Luljak and Steve Percy, Gregory Jay, and Sandra Jones, March 20, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 344)
    - Urban Gardening, with Tom Luljak and Mary Gruhl/Victor Barnett, April 17, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 345)
    - OARSS Program/Non-Traditional Students, with Tom Luljak, April 24, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 346)
    - US Education System, with Tom Luljak and Alfonzo Thurman, May 1, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 347)
    - NovaScan/9-11 and Security, with Tom Luljak and Bill Gregory, May 8, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 348)
    - Roberto Hernandez Center/Milwaukee's Latino Community, with Tom Luljak and Enrique Figueroa, May 15, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 349)
    - The Fine Arts Quartet, with Tom Luljak and Bob Bucker, May 22, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 350)
    - Tornadoes, with Tom Luljak and Paul Roebber, May 29, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 351)
    - PhD Program/Transition from School to College of Nursing, with Tom Luljak and Sally Lundeen, June 12, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 352)
    - Recruitment and Outreach/New Freshmen, with Tom Luljak and Jan Ford, June 19, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 353)
    - Project Ujima/Community Violence and Victimization, with Tom Luljak and Hobart Davies, June 26, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 354)
    - UWM Field Station/Bat Research, with Tom Luljak and Jim Reinhartz, July 10, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 355)
    - Center On Aging And Community/The Elderly And How To Care For Them, with Tom Luljak and Anne Basting, July 17, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 356)
    - Youth Enterprise Academy, with Tom Luljak and Mark Schug, July 24, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 357)
    - UWM's Water Security Center, with Tom Luljak and Val Klump, August 14, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 358)
    - Carnegie Grant, with Tom Luljak and Linda Post, August 21, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 359)
    - Institute of World Affairs, with Tom Luljak and Robert Ricigliano, September 11, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 360)
    - Lifelong Learning, with Tom Luljak and Susan Kelly, September 18, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 361)
    - Executive MBA Program, with Tom Luljak and Mark Mone/Tom Hirsch, October 16, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 362)
    - NSF Award/Center for Mathematics and Science Education Research, with Tom Luljak and DeAnn Huinker, October 23, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 363)
    - UWM Basketball, with Tom Luljak and Bruce Pearl/Sandy Botham, October 30, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 364)
    - Poetry, with Tom Luljak and Lisa Samuels, November 27, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 365)
    - Milwaukee Magazine Article/UWM and Positive Environments for Women, with Tom Luljak and Sona Andrews/ShaRon Williams, December 11, 2003, 1 audio cassette (Audio 366)
    - Science Bag, with Norm Lasca, Robert Greenler and Tom Luljak, January 14, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040115)
    - Drug Use Research, with Mike Allen and Tom Luljak, February 12, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040212)
    - Cultures and Communities, with Karen Thorne, Sarah Stoecker, and Tom Luljak, March 11, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040311)
    - Financial Aid, with Jane Hojan-Clark and Tom Luljak, March 18, 2004, 1 digital audio file (Electronic 20040318)